zaggora.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 19th, 2014. 

ZAGGORA LTD, trading through WWW.ZAGGORA.COM ("ZAGGORA" "we", "our", "us") and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of its online visitors ("you", "your", "yours") and recognise the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We have adopted a corporate wide Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information that you provide us with. As part of our commitment to your privacy rights and security, our website has been certified by Geotrust.

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about ZAGGORA's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with ZAGGORA. 

The following information is provided by ZAGGORA to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By visiting ZAGGORA.COM, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link and ZAGGORA is not responsible for any personal information you submit to third parties via our website. Please ensure that you read the Privacy Policy of such other companies or organizations before submitting your details.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND HOW?**

ZAGGORA collects personal information ("Personal Information") in several ways when you place an order, buy a gift voucher for a friend or register for a service offered by ZAGGORA. By registering, you are consenting to the collection of your personal data. If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including your name, email address, phone numbers, home address, shipping and billing address(es) so that we can process and fulfill your order.

Credit/ debit card details will be saved and processed by SagePay or ChasePaymentech, global online transactions providers, or Paypal. ZAGGORA does not receive your credit card number. Saved card details will never be shared with third parties and will only be used to process your order, using our payment partner's systems. Additionally we may also obtain information as a result of authentication or identity checks. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order. 

**WHAT ABOUT COOKIES?**

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser which tracks your movements within websites. Our site uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, the contents of your shopping cart, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

**HOW THIS INFORMATION MAY BE USED, INCLUDING ANYONE IT MIGHT BE SHARED WITH**

ZAGGORA may use your Personal Information for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. We will also use your details to fulfill and deliver your orders and manage your account. Personal Information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. Your personal information may also be shared with other trading divisions within the ZAGGORA group. Where there is a legal obligation to do so, we may disclose your information to any relevant regulatory body. We may provide access to Personal Information when legally required to do so to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Website, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property, or safety of visitors of this Website or the public.

We may also use your Personal Information to send you marketing updates but only ever in accordance with your preferences (as detailed in the next section). ZAGGORA may disclose your personal information to third parties whom ZAGGORA instructs to provide services on ZAGGORA’s behalf, including, but not limited to, support services, website services, delivering promotional materials, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions, and answering customer questions about ZAGGORA’s products and services. We do not sell your details to third party marketing companies, unless authorized by you at purchase point. 

We do collate statistical information about site traffic, sales and other commercial information which we may pass on to trusted third parties but these statistics do not include any information which can identify you personally. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services.

Finally, we may use your Personal Information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve our site design to better meet our visitors' needs.

From time to time ZAGGORA may employ third party business partners to collect Personal Information on ZAGGORA's behalf. In such cases, these third parties will be subject to confidentiality agreements and instructed by ZAGGORA to comply fully with the ZAGGORA Privacy Policy.

**MARKETING OPT-IN AND OPT-OUT PROVISION**

When you place an order on Zaggora.com, you will be automatically opted in to our regular update service which will send you:

(i) Email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about ZAGGORA, our subsidiaries or selected business partners. 

(ii) Direct mail alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about ZAGGORA, our subsidiaries or selected business partners.

We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes unless authorized by you at purchase point.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update. Any email we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out. Simply follow the instructions in the email. You can also change your email preferences or opt out of all emails by logging into Your Account. Alternatively, to opt out of direct email promotions and updates, please contact a Zaggora customer care representative at customers@zaggora.com.

**HOW YOU CAN ACCESS AND IF NECESSARY, CHANGE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION ZAGGORA MAINTAINS**

If for any reason you are concerned that the Personal Information held by ZAGGORA is not correct, please visit the website and, after logging into the site using the "Sign In" menu on the home page, your personal information will be made available for review and change in the "My Account" section. Only you or, upon your request, the Customer Care department, may access your personal data from the website using your password and User ID. Information may be changed online within My Details, Shipping Details, and My Email Preferences. If you change your billing or shipping address while your order is still being processed, the order will be re-processed through security validation checks. If you prefer, you may contact us by email at customers@zaggora.com and we will amend your personal details. 

**SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We will take reasonable care to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. When you place an order or access your account information, we use a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption which encrypts your information before it is sent to us to protect it from unauthorised use. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners' to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information. 

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to LOG OUT at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

**WHERE AND HOW TO ASK QUESTIONS OR FILE COMPLAINTS**

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the Website where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered.

If you require more information please go to the Contact Us section of the web site and send an email to the relevant ZAGGORA department. If you wish to talk to a ZAGGORA Customer Care representative please write to: c/o Data Protection Officer, ZAGGORA, 2-6 Boundary Row, London, SE1 8HP.

**CALIFORNIA PROVISIONS**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties for direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address:

Legal Department

2-6 Boundary Row

London SE1 8HP

United Kingdom

Please allow 30 days for a response.
